{
    "subject": "Rita_Wilson",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Tom_Hanks",
    "human_readable": "Rita Wilson is married to Tom Hanks.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.988469660282135,
            "question": "Is Tom Hanks married to Rita Wilson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9548388719558716,
            "question": "Is Tom Hanks in a relationship with Rita Wilson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9414112567901611,
            "question": "To whom is Rita Wilson married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9355452656745911,
            "question": "Who is Rita Wilson married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8925024271011353,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Rita Wilson and Tom Hanks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8669202327728271,
            "question": "Name a famous actor who is married to Rita Wilson."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8087611198425293,
            "question": "Who is Rita Wilson's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5519081354141235,
            "question": "What is the name of Tom Hanks' wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13272392749786377,
            "question": "Name a celebrity couple."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09230105578899384,
            "question": "Who are the famous actors who are married to each other?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rita Wilson is married to Tom Hanks.",
            "html": "yago_5976_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a celebrity couple.",
            "html": "yago_5976_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Tom Hanks' wife?",
            "html": "yago_5976_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Rita Wilson's husband?",
            "html": "yago_5976_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5976_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5976_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5976_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5976_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5976_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5976_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5976_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5976_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5976_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5976_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide clear information that supports the statement \"Rita Wilson is married to Tom Hanks.\" The texts repeatedly mention their long-lasting marriage, from meeting on set in 1981 to getting married in 1988 and having two children together."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}